Three, two, one.
Answer Answer Fighting!
Oh, great!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
Shall we?
Oh, my gosh!
One, two, three.
Answer answer answer fighting!
Here we go!
Oh, I got it.
Now where is this place?
This is called the south walkway.
South sidewalk?
In downtown Toyama.
The second or the first? It's a famous shopping district.
Young people often come here.
Oh!
And the food stalls are quite famous.
If you go to the back of the street...
You'll find an old Korean market.
There are a lot of Korean
I think you'll have a lot of fun.
I think you will enjoy it.
Let's get a sense of Korea here.
Okay.
Okay, let's get started.
Let's have them walk around in their beds.
Let's go.
You can see over there, there's a lot of food stalls.
It's famous for movies.
Movies!
There's a film festival there.
We often go to the film festival in Busan.
Is it here?
Yes, it is.
Yay!
Cute.
It's cute.
This is Yakoto.
A young, young girl named Yakoto.
She's famous for Tanya.
Girls from Korea often come here.
They come all the way to Japan.
If it's popular in Japan...
I heard it's popular now.
I thought I'd buy some.
I bought some.
French Carafeen!
I'll pick four things I'm used to from here.
That's pretty much how people said it.
That's all for today.
Love to all of you.
I'm hungry.
Call me
Kanbo dumplings
Looks so delicious!
Delicious!
Eat at the pace of strawberry
this is the hoto one I mentioned earlier
that thing on the right is sweet.
It's a mixture of sunflower seeds
It's a mixture of many things.
Put it inside and eat it!
Uhhh...
Are you ordering?
Later.
I want to order.
What do you want me to say?
When?
Three, please.
Siahoto, please give me three.
Siahoto, please give me three
Three siahot, please.
Six thousand won.
Thank you very much.
It smells so good.
Delicious.
What does it taste like?
Fat.
Not too greasy.
Buttered.
It's, uh...
It's sweet.
It smells so good.
That one comes around the corner.
Ooh.
You're early.
It's tangled.
Hey, it's tangled.
Looks delicious.
It's a really nice color.
I'm hungry.
There's so much here.
What did I leave you with?What did I leave you with?
It's good for this rain.
But it's sweet.
I thought it was sweet.
He's a very famous Korean comedian.
In Japan.
Wednesday.
Those girls are the most popular.
They are the most popular.
Korean comedians.
Yes, Korean comedians.
It's the most famous program, and it's over now, but we watch it together every Saturday.
When you came to Korea before, did you spend much time in the city?
I didn't have time for that at all. I could do a live concert and go out to eat that night.
I was able to go out to eat the same night.
I've never been to a city like this before.
It's so much fun!
I feel like I'm finally in Korea.
Is that what this is?
It's done.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Is it hot?
This looks delicious.
It's so cute.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
How is it?
Crispy.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
And again.
Looks good.
Oh, my God.
It's so crispy and delicious!
Looks delicious.
It's so crunchy and firm inside.
It's delicious.
Looks good.
It's sweet inside.
And there are so many nuts.
It's crunchy and chewy.
It's so good!
Looks delicious!
It's delicious.
Delicious!
Next time, I'll show you some Korean food!
See you soon!
Delicious!
Amazing!
Looks delicious!
Smells so good!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, my God, it's so beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
Ta-da!
Oh, it's not here.
Oh, there it is.
Delicious.
Cute.
Crispy.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
I have no idea what it is.
I still don't know.
Nuts, I guess.
Delicious.
Whip, whip, whip.
Can you see it?
Mmm.
Yummy.
Yum! Yum!
Thank you.
It's hot.
We're all young, aren't we?
We're all in our youth.
Youth.
Not youth
Not youth.
I came here when there was a live start at Takeyama...
Or not?
Again?
I'd like to do it again.
I want to.
Please come then!
Please come.
I'll call you, I'll call you.I'll call you, I'll call you, I'll call you.
I introduced myself in Korean before, didn't I?
I did, didn't I?
You introduced yourself in Korean?
Yes, I did.
I'm Tanaka Sakurahime.
Oh!
Yes, that's correct.
Pleased to meet you.
There are so many of these.
I like this one.
I want some of this.
It's Korean oden.
Oden?
Ddeokbokki?
Oden
Kim-pa?
Yes, sir.
Korean oden
The soup is delicious.
Delicious.
There are a lot of these.
It's true.
It's not spicy.
Japanese spicy?
Japanese?
Not spicy... a little spicy.
A little spicy
Gyoza
Gyoza is delicious.
Wait a minute.
Let's try them
Mandu
Mandu is delicious!
Is this for one person?
It's too much!
This?
Is this for one person?
Maybe two?
Maybe two.
For two?
Maybe.
We're not there yet.
Here you go, sausage.
Sundae.
Sausage.
Inside the pig's guts
Inside the sausage
It's made like that
It's definitely spicy.
Definitely spicy
Looks spicy.
Then I'll have a bite too.
Okano?
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Looks hot
Yum! Delicious!
Is it spicy?
Yes!
Not too spicy?
But I think Sakura will like it.
Here you go.
Here you go. Thanks.
Yes, you're cute.
It's okay.
But there's spicy and not spicy.
I'll take the spicy one.
Even the non-spicy one.
It's so sticky!
Is this ddeokbokki?
Yes, it's tteokbokki.
Did you eat it?
I did.
It's spicy!
Is it spicy?
No, not at all.
Not at all?
Oh, thank you.
I don't know what it is.
It's soup.
Soup? Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Soup?
Soup?Soup?
Delicious.
Thank you, sir.
Is it hot?
Thank you very much.
You can put it over here.
It's so good.
I know why Korean food is so good.
It's delicious.
Delicious!
Delicious
Warming
Is this spicy?
Let's try it.
Not so good?
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
Yes, it's good.
I dare you.
Yum. Yum.
Is it kind of gross?
What?
I don't know what this is.
Chocolate?
It's okay.
It's good.
Is it good?
I've never heard you say it's good.
I've never heard a Japanese say it.
That's right.
That's why.
It's good.
Is it?
I'll try it.
It's good.
Which way did you say it?
Yum.
It's good.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Even the feet?
You're not gonna eat it?
It might be good.
How is it?
It's good.
But there's a little bit of a smell.
Smelly?
It stinks.
No, it's not.
It's big.
It's good.
How much?
How much of what?
A big one.
Is it good?
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Do you like it when I put something dry on the floor?
We'd be happy to have you come inside.
Oh, Mr. Cutispin's bath.
What?
LOL.
I think I'm going to come eat.
Oh, wow.
He's a little small.
He's a big guy.
Oh, it's delicious.
I'm going to have to get my vassion displayed here someday.
LOL.
Japanese tea.
Seriously?
Yes, we have a lot of it in Japan.
I drink it.
For a certain day?
We have a lot of it.
We have a lot of it in Japan.
We have this one.
You don't have this in Japan?
Not in Japan.
What about games?
Do you know?
Usually 200 yen?
That's cheap!
Cheap?
Two hundred yen.
Steal!
Because of Corona, a lot of stores are a little bit closed now.
But originally, there were many more stores.
It was very busy, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
But even now, it's still very busy.
That's the most famous one.
That place is famous.That place is famous.
Even if there's no festival or anything...
There are food stalls like that.
Yes, anytime.
That's nice.
But we do have a film festival.
It'll be more lively then.
Yes, it is.
You can see all kinds of independent films.
Wow! That's great!
When I did it before, Mutiny was only available during festivals.
Most of the time.
So, it's really fun to have a mutiny all the time.
It's like a festival every day.
Yes, yes. Everyday festival.
Cute hat!
Cute.
That's right!
Amazing.
So many hats.
It's so Korean.
Korea.
Would you recommend this?
I think you can wear this.
But...
Ooh!
I can see it.
Cute.
I need a pair of vertical glasses like these.
There are a lot of them.
White ones like these are so Korean.
Do you have white ones in Japan?
But the girls wearing them
They look Korean.
Like she likes Korea.
So cute!
What? It's so cute!
So cute.
She's so cute!
Lira, you definitely look good in it.
It's adorable.
Do you have any favorites?
Something you don't mind?
It's adorable.
The bears are adorable.
And the pink hoodie is cute.
Sure.
I'll change it with a head.
Cute.
The colors are cute
Pokey headset, such a cute one.
Big and cute.
Rehmite was wearing it, and it's so excited.
The image of him wearing it is amazing.
If you look at it like this, it might look like a taco
So cute!
I can imagine him wearing this.
It's so cute!
Good morning.
It's 20 minutes past the hour.
I'm going to leave at 30 minutes.
I'll be able to see this place in 10 minutes.
I'll see if I can make a decision in 10 minutes.
I've got about 30 minutes.
I need a cerity or something.
I went looking for it.
Gut mode.
Gachimode.
So, you guys are all vanilla?
My vanilla flavor.
Introduce me to vanilla.
You know, I've been watching you on YouTube for a long time.
I've always wanted to try it.
Oh, my God, there's ice cream in it.
It's in the marshmallow.
I can't believe they put ice cream inside of marshmallows.
Oh, my God.
And then you bake it.
Oh, my God, it's absolutely delicious.
I'm so happy.
It's like a barbecue
Grilled marshmallows
Smells sweet
Delicious
Juice
Great! That's good!
Wow!
Did you eat it, Mame?
You think she'll eat it?
Bon appétit.
She's crunchy.
Is it good?
It's so good!
Yes, we made it!
We made it! You're fast, surprisingly fast!
Bon appétit!Bon appétit!
Is it good? It's so good!
This is huge! It's huge!
It's twice the size!
Delicious!
I walked around eating them!
They were kind of small, but I didn't realize how big they were!
What's that in between?
Vanilla? Vanilla?
This black stuff? Chocolate? Chocolate?
Like a brulee? Yeah, it's...
Yum! Yum!
It's so sweet! Yes! Alternate!
Cold? Yeah, cold!
It was warm at first! Warm!
Don't you want to eat? I don't want to eat it!
Rico game?
Aah! Rico game!
I'm digging! Let's crunch!
Oh, my gosh!
The star-shaped one.
You want to play it together?
All together?
Just the four triggers?
I'm going to make the pattern all together.
Which would you prefer?
Anything's fine!
Anything?
Easy to do?
Easy! Easy!
And a heart.
And a waist.
Is that a person?
A person?
Cute!
What do you want this one or the heart one?
I think I'll go with this one.
Put the inside like this.
Heh.
Thank you for watching.
Oh!
Ooh!
Looks like it's done.
That's all I need to get my footing.
Oh, my God.
Oh, what the hell? How do you do that?
Tap, tap, crunch, scrape?
Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh.
The tree is making a hole that's going to be far away from the tree.
Oh, but it's amazing.
This is what they do in Italy.
Yes, this is Italy.
If you can make it in time, you will go to the next stage.
Oh, from here?
Oh, but I feel like I can get it.
Oh, this is hard.
It's hard, very hard.
Adotte Ninja Degree Vosco, I'm Anumaan.
Hey, no, are you okay, I'm just handing it out and pouring out the colors.
As long as it's transparent!
Psst!
pfft!
it's so hard!
wow!
Oh, wow!
It breaks here.
Can you do it?
It's gonna break.
Crack?
Hmm?
I think it's gonna break here.
Let's go this way.
Oh, my God!
Oh, thank God.
That's good. You okay?
That was hard.
It's hard.
But there's a crack here.
It's okay. It's okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That was fast!
The middle one is badass, too!
It's awesome! It's got this thing on it.
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Oh no! Oh, man!
This is fun!
Not yet!
Can we not break this?
Can't we break it?
Don't break it!
It's still good!
How much is this?How much is this?
About 2,000 yen?
About 2,000 yen.
What should I do with it?
I don't know if it looks good on me.
I'm so indecisive when it comes to choosing clothes.
All the time.
I'll buy something after I've had a hard time.
You should ask a friend to go with you.
I need them to help me decide.
I need my mom to tell me what would look good on me.
I can't make up my mind.
I can't take the plunge.
That's right.
Isn't 2,000 yen a lot cheaper?
2,000 yen is a lot cheaper.
2,000 yen in Japan is not so bad.
It would be cute if it wasn't!
Ehhhh...
If you put it this way...
It doesn't match the gray.
It's true.
It's also to your liking.
Hey, it's your choice.
It's pretty, but...
Leila, it's a sad fact that gray doesn't suit you.
Oh, really?
It doesn't suit me. My mom says
She says I don't look good in gray.
Do you think you can do this?
I think I can do it!
Even in the skirt you're wearing now.
Even in your current state
It looks great on you!
I think I'll buy it.
It could be a thank you.
I think it will be
I think I'll buy it.
I'm going to buy it
Decided!
We've got four minutes.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Oh, my God!
I don't know.
I can do it.
I think so.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Okay, okay.
Wait a minute.
Here.
Oh.
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
But why not stick takoyaki on it?
A-ha-ha-ha
Sure, sure, sure.
Oh!
There it is!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
He was a little dead.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I lost my head.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What's coming?
I don't know.
It's like you're a great craftsman.
You seem like you'd be good at that.
You look like you're good at it.
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
I'm not supposed to be like this.
I'm gonna be a little more human.
It's a head.
It's cute.
It's fun.
Looks like a crescent moon, doesn't it?
Crescent moon.
Crescent moon indeed.
Skirt.
Skirt?
It's time to go.
Oh, are you coming?
Oh, no, no, no.
One more time.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come again?
Go, go, go, go, go.
Okay.
I got my groceries.
He's cute.
Here you go.
Oh!
That's so cute.cute
Cute.
Oh! Does it look good on me?
It looks good on you.
Korean.
If you put this on and wear this...
Kanpoi.
I like it.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
Next time
extra
Run.
go for it!
Go for it.
That's great.
Your back looks really tight, doesn't it?
It's a hard back.
Do you know what they say? Korean people...
Everybody knows that in the middle of the video clip.
Do you know everyone?
Everybody knows.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you very much.
How was the exchange?
It was my first time to meet Japanese high school students
I met with Korean university students.
The Korean students are very interested in Japan.
I was very happy to see that Korean people are interested in Japan, and high school students were very active in the exchange.
I was very happy to see that.
I hope it will lead to more and more opportunities for the future.
It was a lot of fun!
Thank you very much.
At first, I couldn't read Korean or understand what they were saying
I was anxious at first because I couldn't read Korean or understand what they were saying.
But Korean students and people in town were very warm and friendly.
I was able to enjoy Korea with peace of mind.
I would like to do this kind of tour again because I have a longing for Korea.
It was a lot of fun.
I had been to Musashi for quite a while.
I had been to Musashi for a long time and had a chance to communicate with Japanese students and Korean students.
I had been to Musashi for quite a while and had interacted with Japanese and Korean students only once before.
I was impressed by the fresh reactions of the high school students to everything.
Also, the kindness of the Korean people.
I was able to experience a lot of things that are usually hard to experience just by coming on a trip.
I hope that if Korean students come to Japan again, I will be able to enjoy taking them to even more places.
I was so excited to think about what kind of places I could take them to and what kind of fun they would have.
I was really excited and thinking about it.
It was a lot of fun.
I used to make curry with Korean and Japanese students who came to Chest Shoulder
I made curry with Korean students who came to Chest Shoulder and Japanese students who came to Chest Shoulder.
At that time, I think I was the one to tell them about Japan and the goodness of Chest Shoulder.
But this time, I came to Pusan
I think I was the one to tell the students about the good points of Korea and
I had a lot of fun learning about the good things about Korea and the delicious food.
I also had a lot of fun, and the students asked me a lot of questions like "What is this? What is this? and "What is this?
I thought it was very nice that the students were so enthusiastic and eager to learn.
It made me think that we should do our best too.
I came to Busan by boat for the first time.
I came to Pusan by boat for the first time, but it only takes 4 hours by Queen Beetle.
I think it's very fast.
I think it's very fast to come here in 4 hours.
I hope we can deepen our relationship with each other in this short distance.
We also want to visit Pusan more often.
Yes, this is my first time in Korea and I'm really looking forward to it.
I was really looking forward to this first time in Korea, but I was so close to the high school students.
I was a little nervous at first, but I was so happy to talk with them.
But I was happy to talk with them a lot.
The college students told us about their favorite places in Korea and how to do things.
and how to do things in Korea.
I was able to experience a lot of things that I couldn't do on my trip.
I was able to experience a lot of things that I wouldn't have been able to do on a trip, and I have wonderful memories.
It was a really fun time!
It was so much fun!
I had such a great time that I think I could have stayed longer.
I could have stayed longer!
Korean students taught me a lot of things about Korea
and playing games with them.
I was also able to talk a lot with Japanese students.
I think that the bond between us has deepened, and I would like to continue to have many more exchanges in the future.
I hope we can have many more exchanges in the future.
Thank you very much for your time.
How was the exchange this time?
It was for two days.
I think we had a very fulfilling and enjoyable exchange.
The two members of "One Tension" made it so much fun.
I think the Korean sensibilities are having a lot of fun right now.
I am so happy!
I hope this exchange will lead to the next and the next
I think that we were able to keep the day going.I think we could have done it without the day disappearing, so
I'll be working with the two guys from One Tension again in the future.
I hope to make the local exchange you just mentioned more exciting.
Best regards.
Thank you very much.
Let's come back to Takeyama again!
Yes, sir!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
See you soon!
I'll be back!
We'll be back!
See you soon!
Please subscribe to our channel!